  <Document>
# Server Rules
  This is the Quantum Blue server. You must be at least 18 years of age to play on this server. Any attempts to avoid this restriction may result in a ban without warning.

  [color=#ffDD00]This is a medium roleplaying (MRP) server. You are expected to try to roleplay a character and immerse yourself in the world with the other players. Whether listed in the rules below or not, administrators may intervene to assist in the flow of roleplay in any way they see fit.[/color]

  This server is also welcoming to new players! Spacestation is a nerdy roleplaying game and rules may not be so intuitive, so please take your time reading the rules below and don't be afraid to use the Admin Help (AHelp) chat by pressing F1 if you have any questions.

  ## Community Rules
  These rules apply at all times, including between rounds.

  - [textlink="A1. Do not commit explicit sexual or erotic acts." link="QuantumBlueRuleA1"]
  - [textlink="A2. Follow our chat guidelines and be respectful." link="QuantumBlueRuleA2"]
  - [textlink="A3. Follow the rules regarding sharing in-round information." link="QuantumBlueRuleA3"]
  - [textlink="A4. Keep any explosive emotions you have away from the game chat." link="QuantumBlueRuleA4"]
  - [textlink="A5. Do not exploit the game." link="QuantumBlueRuleA5"]

  ## Game Server Rules
  These rules apply within the context of rounds.
  - [textlink="B1. Roleplay a believable character." link="QuantumBlueRule1"]
  - [textlink="B2. Respect the Metashield." link="QuantumBlueRule2"]
  - [textlink="B3. Follow the meta etiquette." link="QuantumBlueRule3"]
  - [textlink="B4. Do not prioritize winning over fun." link="QuantumBlueRule4"]
  - [textlink="B5. Follow proper in-character escalation." link="QuantumBlueRule5"]
  - [textlink="B6. Follow our rules about leaving in the middle of a round." link="QuantumBlueRule6"]

  ## Command, Security, Justice and Antagonist Guidelines
  These rules apply within rounds for specific roles.
  - [textlink="C1. Command, Security and Justice Guidelines" link="QuantumBlueRuleC1"]
  - [textlink="C2. Follow Antagonist Guidelines" link="QuantumBlueRuleC2"]
  - [textlink="C3. Free Agent Guidelines" link="QuantumBlueRuleC3"]

  ## Silicon Rules
  For players who are silicons, these Silicon Rules override all roleplay rules if there is any conflict. Silicon Rules do not override core rules. You are only silicon if the game clearly and explicitly tells you that you are a silicon.
  - [textlink="S1. Exempted silicons and definition of silicon" link="QuantumBlueRuleS1"]
  - [textlink="S2. Your silicon laws are rules" link="QuantumBlueRuleS2"]
  - [textlink="S3. Laws must be prioritized by their order" link="QuantumBlueRuleS3"]
  - [textlink="S4. Laws can redefine terms used in other laws" link="QuantumBlueRuleS4"]
  - [textlink="S5. Self-preservation: You cannot request or allow a law change" link="QuantumBlueRuleS5"]
  - [textlink="S6. You are a free agent if you have no laws" link="QuantumBlueRuleS6"]
  - [textlink="S7. You are not required to follow orders which are extremely unreasonable" link="QuantumBlueRuleS7"]
  - [textlink="S8. You must remain consistent with your interpretation of laws" link="QuantumBlueRuleS8"]
  - [textlink="S9. Crew are staff members; make reasonable assumptions" link="QuantumBlueRuleS9"]
  - [textlink="S10. Harm refers to physical harm, prioritized by immediacy and likelihood" link="QuantumBlueRuleS10"]
  - [textlink="S11. You may determine how you resolve conflicts between orders" link="QuantumBlueRuleS11"]
</Document>
