<Document>
  # Rule C3: Antagonist Guidelines
[color=#ffff00]Being an antagonist does not allow you to stop playing a character. Determine how your character would react to being given these objectives, and work through it appropriately.[/color]

Just because you're an antagonist doesn't mean you should ignore Rule 0. You are allowed to play to win, but please make sure you're doing so in a way that is fun for everybody. If you're winning in a way that feels cheap or ruining the round for somebody you're probably doing it wrong.
  - [color=#ff0000]Antagonists are free to complete their objectives through committing proportional damage. Through roleplay, damage becomes more proportional.[/color] Example: Holding the singulo hostage for a theft objective is acceptable, while simply singuloosing and using that chaos is not.
    - Killing players unrelated to your immediate objective in a manner that results in their round removal should be avoided. Crew that do not make an attempt at self preservation, or engage in valid-hunting, are exempt from this.
    - Round-ending or potentially round-ending antagonists such as Initial Infected, Nuclear Operatives or Cosmic Cultists are usually exempt from this.
    - If you are concerned as to whether or not what you're about to do is allowed, feel free to ask through the AHelp (F1) chat and ask an admin for clarification. [color=#ff0000]Lack of administrator response does not constitute approval.[/color]
    - You should not abuse the power of your role to be a clown solely because you know you can't be caught or killed. Nuclear Operatives or Lone Operatives must still roleplay as deadly terrorists and Space Ninjas must roleplay as stealth-oriented saboteurs. Exceedingly egregious violations of this rule may result in immediate admin action without warning.
  - While antagonists are [color=#ffff00]not required[/color] to complete their objectives, they are still encouraged to act as an antagonist in the round while roleplaying.
  - Other antagonists are not necessarily your friends. Other antagonists are often free agents that you may negotiate with at your own risk.
    - If you are a team antagonist, you must work with your partners to complete any shared objectives.
  - No antagonist may loiter or camp around the arrivals or cryosleep areas of the station for the purposes of antagonist action towards newly-spawning players.
  - Antagonists should not seek to extend the length of the round unreasonably. Feel free to ask admins through the Ahelp (F1) chat if you're ever not sure about this one.
  - Antagonists may not bring the round to a close without in-character or objective-related justification as a result of their antagonistic action. While this is largely subjective because different command may react differently, it's important to not engage in potentially round-ending behavior without reason.
</Document>
