<Document>
# Rule B1: Roleplay a believable character.
You must roleplay a character separate from yourself, the player. Try to keep your character's feelings, emotions and actions separate from your own as the player.
  - Try to act in-character and do as your character would in that situation.
  - Let people do their own jobs, only help if requested or explicitly allowed. Remember that they queued up for that role to play it, if you're doing their job for them you're likely only taking that away from them.
  - Being an antagonist does not allow you to stop playing a character. Determine how your character would react to being given these objectives, and work through it appropriately.
  - Do not annoy other players without any roleplay or IC reason, and even then be careful not to just come across as an asshole.

## Rule B1.1: Follow the naming convention rules.
  - In-character names must not make obvious references nor be too over the top of a play on words, and must not be obscene. Cheesy names are okay, but don't be surprised if you're told to change your name from "Greyson Tidus". Use the Ahelp (F1) chat if you're not sure about a character name!
  - Theatrical roles such as the clown, boxer, mime and others (within reason) are allowed much more freedom in their names.

## Rule B1.2: Communicate in character
  - Do not use the Emote channel to bypass an inability to speak, such as when playing a Zombie.
  - Do not use Netspeak in character (lol, brb, wtf, etc) unless if in an in-character text form (Nanochat, letters, drawings or anything of the sort).
  - Do not discuss Out Of Character (OOC) matters In Character (IC).
  - Do not engage in meta-communications (i.e. using discord to exchange in-round information with another person also present in that round).

## Rule B1.3: If you die and return to life, follow the new life rules.
If a player dies, they forget the specific details of their death. [color=#ff0000]Please report players who break this rule.[/color] A cyborg being removed from its chassis is not a death, and may decide for itself whether or not it experiences memory loss.
  - If revived through any means, they can only recall vague information such as “Someone shot me” or “I was set ablaze”, and generally only clearly remember events up to around 5 minutes before their death.
  - A character entering critical state can still remember any events leading up to it, unlike as if they died. You're still encouraged to roleplay it out to some capacity instead of preparing a very elaborate paragraph to send as soon as you're back from crit.
  - If you have any questions about this, please ask an admin through the Ahelp (F1) chat. As a rule of thumb though, just keep other people's fun in mind whenever deciding what information to share when your character is back up.
</Document>
