<Document>
  # Rule B5: Follow proper in-character escalation.
  - As a crew member on the space station, you are allied with Nanotrasen and the station as a whole from the start of the round.
  - Do not act like an antagonist if you are not an antagonist.
  - Willfully assisting known antagonists is self-antagonism.
     - Leeway is given in the case of bribes, coercion, or other forms of duress.
  - Actively seeking conversion or transformation into an antagonist is considered self-antag.
  - Clowns, Mimes, and theater roles are expected to "entertain" the crew, and should not be committing regular felonies to do so.
  - End-of-round grief (EORG) is not allowed. This means attacking, destroying, polluting, and severely injuring without reason after the shuttle has docked at Central Command. Remember that you are playing a character throughout the round, and our roleplay rules do not evaporate at Central Command.

  As crew you can still commit some degree of self-antagging if you parse it through very believable roleplay. Have an In Character reason for attacking other players, whether they are in a ghost role or not. The required reason depends on the situation and while the rule of thumb is to follow rule 0, please use the Ahelp (F1) menu to ask an admin if you're ever unsure.
  - Escalation should move up slowly or at the same pace as the other character you're interacting with. A disagreement may lead to insults, then possibly to non-lethal aggression and so on. This means no jumping from insults to gunshots without VERY GOOD REASON.
  - Killing is also allowed to crew-aligned jobs and roles provided very good and believable roleplay, and so long as you do not prevent their rescue and are both escalating naturally it should be fine.
  - In the extreme cases of wanting to cause round-removal as a crew-aligned character, please either make sure the other player is okay with it before you do it and discuss it with an admin through Ahelp (F1) first.
  - Antagonists do not have to obide by these rules (but are still encouraged to try), but in either case non-antagonists must still respect escalation rules against antagonists.

</Document>
